

Giovanni Trevisan

.NET Developer / Fullstack Developer

DETAILS

Barueri Brazil +55 11 949200184 gitrevizzo194@gmail.com

NATIONALITY Brazilian

DATE OF BIRTH April 2, 2000

LANGUAGES

Portuguese	
English	
SKILLS	
C# .NET	
HTML & CSS	
SQL	
Git	
API Development	
JavaScript	
TypeScript	
React	
API Testing	
Angular	

Profile

I've been a Developer for 4 years, I'm 22 years old and I have a great passion for programming and development, I'm very interested in new technologies. I'm able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. I'm proficient in an assortment of technologies, including .NET C#, IIS and Microsoft SQL Server.

Employment History

.Net Developer, Wiz Soluções

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

- 1. Development of a Product to improve the system and user experience, in addition to integrating systems and products from Consortiums for large companies such as <u>Santander</u>, <u>Caixa Seguros</u> and others.
- 2. Improvement of Legacy APIs or creating new APIs (.Net Core 3.1 and Later) and helping with front-end development (Angular)

.Net Developer, LG Lugar de Gente

DECEMBER 2019 - APRIL 2022

- 1. Full-stack developer with a focus on Back-end (*C# .NET*). along with a team of development in support and improvement of the company's LMS (Learning Management System) tool for its customers such as <u>Anglogold Ashanti</u>, <u>Riachuelo</u>, <u>Fast Shop</u> among others.
- 2. Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.

Fullstack Developer, Infopack Sistemas

DECEMBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2019

1. Full-stack Developer (*PHP*) development of the company's system. Worked on ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) development.

Education

FIAP University

2022 - 2023

MBA in Full Stack Developer Design, Engineering & Deployment

FIAP University

2019 - 2020

Graduation in Digital Games

Technical education at FITO

2015 - 2018

IT technical course

Courses

Responsive Web Developing, FIAP - 2021

Web & Game Developing, FIAP - 2020

Unity Mobile, FIAP - 2020

